MY BELOVED DEMON
There is none.
We managed to survive.
I thought that really...
who are you
Who are you anyway?
What did you do to me?
EPISODE 2
EVERYONE HAS A DEMON IN THEIR HEART
Mrs. To.
- Ms. Sin.
- Is everything okay?
I just had a nightmare.
What exactly did you dream about? You sweated.
Glad to see you've recovered.
I was very worried.
Do I still have nightmares?
relax The horror is over.
I took you to the hospital after
when he called me
To the hospital?
God Am I hurt?
I don't have time for that.
- How long was I unconscious?
- If exactly,
then you slept deeply for 5 hours and 38 minutes.
Then I slept.
How do you feel?
Dizzy, can't move your hands?
Is something bothering you?
- Why are you behaving so strangely?
- Lie down a little.
you should rest
until the doctor says it's okay.
I'll go get a doctor.
What?
What did you do?
What are you talking about?
Yes, it already looks like you.
You are not at all gentle and attentive.
You didn't want me
considered your ex.
So I showed courtesy, as you asked.
Now they think we are dating.
You don't like everything, what should I do?
The police arrested the attacker,
who hit us with a car?
He will be arrested soon.
I gave them a detailed description.
It should be very simple.
But are you sure everything is okay?
I'm in pain
and in general everything is fine with me.
It seems that with you...
everything is fine
Unfortunately, everything is completely wrong with me.
That's why I was waiting for you.
What?
What kind of tattoo sticker is this?
"Sticker tattoo"?
What is this abomination on my hand?
"Abomination"?
What do you think you are doing?
- No need.
- Does not rub off.
Godi You can spoil it.
Not at all.
Is this a real tattoo?
What happened last night?
Good. You start to remember.
It would be bad if you didn't already know...
Am I that drunk?
Are we in Honte or what?
Why didn't you try to turn me down?
Okay, I'll destroy the tattoo with a laser.
No lasers!
what are you doing step away
Through my corpse.
And how can you stop me?
How about I destroy him with a laser
shall I hide Pororo?
Pororo?
Don't even touch your wrist.
Are you…
you will regret it.
- This is my wrist.
- This is my dad.
What kind of delusion is this?
For unknown reasons
it's on your wrist now
but this is my dad.
are you crazy
- Let go.
- No.
- I say, let it go.
- I say, no.
Better let go.
No.
Who knows what you will do with it?
This is the last warning.
One, two, three.
Why can't I…
That's it.
I knew that.
I didn't want to hit that hard.
I tried to force my hand to move.
How dare you steal mine
when did i save you
Steal?
I must have gone crazy.
Should have just left you
to kill you
This is my cue.
It was necessary to leave
such a scoundrel is food for fish.
I just saved you
so as not to drown. Do you want my tattoo?
Of course. I saved you!
How do you feel?
Doctor, can you examine...
I am very embarrassed.
Sorry?
Let me check my eyes.
Sir, she's not going to be okay, is she?
No, I mean… She'll be fine, right?
Signs of exhaustion disappeared.
- It seems that everything is fine.
- What?
What are you talking about, doctor?
I'm sure I'm crazy.
Mrs. To is an extraordinary person.
Her sense of humor does not betray her
even in hard times.
Of course. Then…
His name was Jung Ku Won?
Are you about a good and rude victim?
I thought about him.
Why?
I wonder where he buys his clothes.
Is it expensive?
I'd look good in that too, right?
You don't want his clothes.
- And what?
- His face, body
and his entire existence.
Congratulations.
I'm Sergeant Park Kyung-soo, I'm handling your case.
You are still here.
I wanted to make sure everything was okay.
As you can see, everything is quite good.
So you can go.
What a relief to hear that.
I asked them not to tell anyone
including Chu's head.
Good.
sorry to bother you
but we need your application.
The most important thing is to catch the criminal.
by the way
I heard you met on a blind date.
Considering what happened
maybe you two should get married.
- No.
I don't plan to get married.
I plan to be alone all my life.
But they went on a blind date.
There is a saying.
"Blind dates and accidents
sometimes become beyond our control"
You may equally be partly to blame
because they did not keep their distance.
EXPIRATION OF THE AGREEMENT
I have to go somewhere.
Of course, go.
Respect yourself, Mrs. To To Hee.
Stay away until we meet
from lasers and Poro...
And Pororo.
Be there.
Write it down. "Lazers and Pororo".
Let it be between us.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR JEONG KOO WON
"DEMON"
Give it back
"Demons exist for deals.
If the demon does not make a deal
does not complete them on time,
spontaneous combustion will begin..."
"Spontaneous combustion"?
Do not touch my things!
What? I am your employee. We are almost a family...
hold on
How did you find her? I am her
hid it where no one would find it.
I was just cleaning and…
Just give it a look.
As your butler I have the right
read the instructions to the demons.
"Instructions"?
What am I to you, a vacuum cleaner?
And what is it then?
Here is all the information about me.
What can you call this instrument...
What?
But this is very important.
So don't go near her.
I'm serious.
by the way
spontaneous combustion
means you'll burn out?
God, how scary.
How often should you enter into new agreements?
Weekly? Monthly?
I don't know.
That's why I'm even more worried.
I knew so.
All that hard work
did not seem inherent in you.
Time already.
Learn all about this woman.
CEO TO TO HI
- "To To Hee"?
- About her family,
blood group
former relationships, roommates,
even her main preferences, in particular,
her tansuyuk sauce
like on a dish or on its own.
Who is this woman that you are so fascinated by her?
The woman I met yesterday
so you are interested?
- She is a thief.
- Did she steal your heart?
I really don't like your look.
Wait, it's not there.
What? What is not?
Tattoo
That's what you're talking about.
What am I talking about?
Has anything else disappeared?
No.
If you think about it, you seem different.
Absolutely not. What are you talking about?
- No?
- No.
OK.
Your powers are gone.
This is something new.
Hold on.
If the strength is gone, then you will burn to ashes,
and I will suddenly become unemployed?
I still have to pay off my new car!
Is that what worries you the most?
It's terrible, I'm out of energy!
You have lost your strength. I was right.
No, I didn't lose them.
- I just...
- What?
I lent them to someone for a short time.
That is, to this thief? What happened?
I don't know.
Whatever she did, my strength
stopped listening
and dad moved to her.
- We need more details.
- Then.
Where are you? To regain strength?
The agreement expires today. This is the main thing.
What can you do without your strength?
What are you talking about? I am a demon.
I've been a demon for at least 200 years.
Collecting souls is not more difficult for me,
than chewing gum.
Do not spit chewing gum everywhere.
You know how difficult it is to remove dried chewing gum from…
What do you think? Do you like it?
to be honest
I've never worked so hard
even at the Olympics.
Although it is very touching,
time to say goodbye beautifully.
I figured it out here.
A deal that asks too much
is considered a dishonest instrument.
That is, I do not owe you anything.
I'm so sick of it.
People are becoming more and more shameless.
It seems that you do not understand who you are dealing with.
So I'll show you now.
Attack one at a time.
He wants to show something. attack
Ahead. Let's see what he can do.
I said one at a time.
One at a time.
How dare you!
Where is the sportsmanship?
Attack him!
Haven't I hit you yet?
Why are you all so alike?
From the road.
I really didn't want to do this, but…
Just wait.
I'll show you, don't forget the contract.
Go ahead, you fool.
show me
To the scoundrel.
Don't drop it!
I sent your battered car to the junkyard
and got you a new one.
He just ate alone in the same restaurant
and came to the coastal road
that evening
It can't just be a coincidence.
I am 100% sure that it is…
Fate?
I didn't know you were so romantic.
Excuse me for being romantic.
He thought of something.
He must be with me all the time
waiting for the right moment.
To do what?
To make a deal with me.
He talked all about the deal,
when I almost died
What can it be about
if he is ready for this?
That's right.
I don't think it's worth my time.
The fact that he is so stubborn and cunning,
means that the deal is mutually beneficial.
Did you get a tattoo?
You have to stop drinking.
It's only been 24 hours
after the release of the article about sugar,
and we already have a 10% drop in shares.
Foreign shareholders
and organizations sell like crazy.
Shall we go to the office?
You will die because of Choo Jung Suk.
I want to see Ms. Chu first.
Detective Paku, the photo robot is ready.
See what details.
He will be caught very quickly.
How can I help?
I noticed that the rent
always paid on time,
but I never see anyone here.
I am the owner of this building.
Can I speak to the director?
No, the troupe is on tour.
I will tell the director to call you.
wait
You seem familiar. are you an actor
- Yes.
- How long have you been working here?
Why have I never seen you?
I recently came back after a break.
You probably won't run away from your calling.
You are right.
After trying, I can't stop.
God
Why is your hand covered in blood?
It? Special makeup.
You might think you killed a person or something.
Please tell the director
that I want to meet
Actually...
BLUE NIGHT THEATER
Our ceiling is leaking.
Started again?
can you look
THE PERFORMANCE IS GOING ON
DO NOT ENTER
- Mrs. Chu.
- Hello.
Is everything ready?
Yes, I'm fine.
Glad to hear that.
Doesn't that calm you down?
It wasn't that bad, was it?
But I just wasted my time.
I wonder how my little plants are doing.
We must hurry home and fertilize them.
Let me give you a ride.
Aren't you busy?
I saw that the market value of the business
fell by 260 million.
I oppose it.
Who was it?
I don't know yet.
Need my help?
leave it
I've been doing great on my own so far.
It would be difficult
need your help right now.
Ms. Chu.
Come in.
- Mrs. Chu.
- Doctor Choi.
You shouldn't have come to me.
I wanted to make sure
that you were comfortable here.
God.
Everyone has already bowed.
I don't see any changes.
How can you not see?
All the leaves have fallen
while I was gone
You need to rest.
Don't complain about your knees later.
I won't.
I have a whole bunch of pills.
Do you consider pain relievers vitamins?
You drink them so regularly.
I will help Just tell me what to do.
leave it You can't do anything.
Just sit down.
You should not load your knees at all.
All those painkillers will hurt you.
Do you have an addiction or something?
Painkillers are no worse than your grunting.
Pain is simply a part of aging.
It would be worse if I just sat there.
A little
Look at the bud.
How complete.
Will bloom soon.
What a beauty.
I wanted to ask you something.
ask
You sometimes…
These hesitations are not like you.
You're not hiding anything from me, are you?
Of course I hide it.
My veins are not blood, but lies.
Business owners can't be honest.
Ms. Chu.
I'm serious.
If you want, I will be honest.
Are you sure you're not hiding anything?
Exactly.
You notice everything equally.
OK.
I will take your word for it.
After all, you're the only one I can trust.
Did someone say something?
I just got curious.
Stupid
Aunt Jung Suk!
Just look, working
immediately after discharge.
I told her to rest, but she doesn't listen.
I did not manage to raise children well,
therefore, plants are the only hope.
But lately everyone is behaving well.
I know Suk Min has changed dramatically.
Think about his age.
It's long overdue.
I tried so hard
that at least something would reach him.
Here is last quarter's earnings report.
It looks good.
Don't just look at the result.
Appreciate the process too.
I worked so hard.
Is it necessary?
She never praises me.
I'll go now.
I'm coming too, To Hee.
But you just came.
I have to hurry to the office
multiply your wealth.
- Are you in your office?
- Yes.
you two
If all you have in life is work,
maybe you two will get married?
Shall we get married?
Sorry?
Don't laugh. What's wrong with you?
What is so funny here?
You are not related, not registered as a family.
You are funny, aunty.
Ignore her, Seok Hoon.
She really wants to marry me now.
I will go, Ms. Chu.
God knows what else you'll say
if i don't go
Okay, I guess that's unlikely.
- I will come again.
- Don't come.
- Are you going straight to the office?
- Yes.
Can I give you a ride?
Wait, I think you came here.
Actually, no.
I didn't come.
I took a taxi.
Great, let me give you a ride.
- Really?
- Let's go. Haven't ridden for a long time.
Sounds great. Come on.
What is it? Are you confused by something?
No, everything is fine, To Hee.
Looks like you're comfortable, Ms. Sin.
Thank you for giving me time
finish your work
Not worth the gratitude.
Shouldn't we give thanks somehow?
to Mr. Jung Ku Won?
He had already paid for the meal.
Probably worth it.
I think I owe him.
Who is it about?
one man
with whom I went on a blind date.
Are you okay, To Hee?
Yes, everything is fine.
Mrs. Sin.
You have a nosebleed.
- God.
- From both...
From both nostrils... Shut up.
Are you sure you're all right, Ms. Sin?
Everything will be fine if I drive.
Sorry.
It was so shocking that I was
on a blind date?
You're just so young.
And it doesn't look like you.
Why did you go on a blind date?
Why else?
Do you want to get married?
That's not the point.
Ms. Chu begged me.
I have no plans to get married.
Then I don't plan either.
What are you talking about?
Well, since you don't plan on getting married,
I thought that it is so fashionable among young people now.
From what? From kimchi?
From spicy noodle soup?
This is yesterday.
And the tie is half untied. show me
you look perfectly normal
but forever such a slob.
My parents are hippies, remember?
We will try to buy
plenty of "Kharchuvannya Mire" shares,
to level the losses.
That's how the rumor goes
about stock manipulation
and internal sales.
Even from an investment point of view
buying your shares is profitable.
Don't worry.
I will take care of myself.
I forgot for a moment how wonderful you are.
And how strong you are. You almost killed me.
- Let me try again.
- No, I like it.
So pretty, Ms. Xin?
Yes, very much.
No wonder you're a trendsetter, To Hee.
- No need to tease me.
- I'm not teasing.
And how you tease! Allow me one more time.
- Hold on.
- It doesn't look like that.
- I will try again.
- No, everything is fine.
I can't find anything.
No mention of a tattoo transition,
not to mention their return!
"DEMON"
Mr. Pak, have you learned anything about To To Hee?
The name is To To Hee.
Third blood group.
Known as the princess of "Mire Group",
"The devil wears Hermes",
Crazy To To Hee,
and this is not the end of the list.
DEVIL
- No!
- This is the Devil!
We pulled out the Devil today!
She is not from a chaebol family.
Her father was an engineer,
developed a metal one
cross bearing for electronics.
Her mother had a hair salon.
She was the only daughter of a late marriage.
But they died in an accident
on her birthday 17 years ago.
To To Hee was then 11 years old.
Then the head of Chu "Mire Group"
sheltered the orphan To To Hee.
Chairman Choo with To Hee's father
were co-founders
"Mire Electronics",
of the main company "Mire Group".
These arrows remind me
situation in the company.
The same feeling as from the songs
about the breakup when you were left.
I did not experience this.
It's because you've never been left.
you say
that my emotions are deeper than then
when did I break up with my exes?
She worked like crazy all her life.
Always better in studies,
even graduated from university early.
She founded it as a student
dessert company
which has become better in seven years.
Then she moved to "Mire Nutrition"
after the acquisition of "Mire Group".
"MIRE NUTRITION"
Until tomorrow, our company has…
go up again
Despite everything.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, madam.
The morning is not good now.
We lost 260 billion won.
Now we are constantly
we publish rebuttal articles.
They don't work.
We will act against fake news
and hateful comments by law.
That doesn't work either.
Maybe we'll just wait?
You see, everything passes with time.
- It's very...
- Powerful?
...poetically absurd.
He is a master of humanities.
Try your hand at the essay contest.
You won't win.
Sorry.
Do you know why the dinosaurs died out?
Since I have a degree in natural sciences,
I will answer this question.
A catastrophic collision occurred
Earth with a comet.
Their quality of work
did not correspond to their size.
That's why they died out.
I have Ms. No Soo Ahn's schedule.
Don't try to tame problems
when they have already happened.
attack
This mess will be cleaned by a person
who arranged it.
Now she is single.
Her past relationships
did not last long because of her preoccupation.
And about the dansuyuk...
Sauce on top!
What? The sauce should be separate!
But this is not the problem now.
I will go there myself, so talk to me
with the lawyers and let me know.
Let me take you away.
Didn't you say that my word is law?
I shouldn't have let you go yesterday.
Just unlucky.
Neither you nor I are to blame.
- Anyway...
- I don't want to become a weak person,
who blames herself and others.
That would mean the scoundrel got me.
And this cannot be allowed.
I have to stay strong.
So far I don't know anything else.
So what's the plan?
I will do what I do best.
And what is it?
Enchant…
people
You look great.
Probably, Mire Nutrition is in chaos right now.
Again, how much have they lost?
Almost 20% before the stock exchange closes.
Poor To Hee.
One article in the news can do this.
Send her flowers to comfort her?
Not worth it. Attention is important.
what are you doing here
What else? Came for shopping.
Do you really have time to shop here?
Shopping takes money, not time.
As the head of Odyah Mire,
you choose clothes better than men.
What a show it was
in front of my employees?
I was just worried about you.
Were you worried about me?
Stock prices may still rise,
but when personal life is exposed,
this is the end
What is your private life like?
You might think
that I'm doing something crazy...
You are not the only one interested in me.
I'm interested in you too.
I carefully hid my actions.
How do you generally…
I spent more money than you.
Falling in love is not a crime
and doing it in public is a crime.
Are you blackmailing me?
Not at all.
I haven't even started yet.
Sorry.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
- Jung Ku Won?
- Can we meet?
I feel very bad after the accident.
How bad is it?
So much so that my existence suffers.
Before, it seemed that everything was fine.
See for yourself if you don't believe.
Come to Taehyun shopping center in Chamsil.
I don't have much time for you.
I won't wait long.
This is my time katma.
Sorry about that.
Listen, Su An.
And here is blackmail.
If about your passionate private life
the public will know
the image of "Mire Clothing" will fall to the bottom.
And this is not the end.
Ms. Chu will blow the roof off.
Don't say a word to her.
Will you regret it?
How sad.
There are no secrets between us.
How about this one?
Clean up the mess you made.
And I will hide the unpleasant truth.
there are things
which are better kept secrets, right?
I advise you not to waste your energy on me.
if you want war
go play with your brother
Father.
I can't…
go to heaven, right?
But there is that...
what am I more afraid of...
than go to hell.
I'm afraid…
that she will not forgive me.
Your own mind has locked you in hell.
Time to confess and tell the truth
to free yourself.
True...
MY DEAR DAUGHTER TO HI
I wonder if Principal Jeon did this.
I trust him completely
when it comes to charming people.
He charmed me not once, but twice.
I thought that was the last smell
there will be incense for me
but I can smell burning coals.
It was so hard to find clients
but the old woman with the scythe was easily found.
Congratulations!
Jesus?
No, not him.
Then?
AGREEMENT FOR THE SALE OF THE SOUL
NETWORK INSTRUCTIONS
"TOPPOKKI KING OF HELL"
so you say
that I only need to put a print here?
Yes. Then a whole network of 2,000 establishments
will be yours
It's a little thing.
Hell can't be worse
during the life of the owner of a small establishment.
I will do it. Give me the ink.
what are you doing
It hurts!
The agreement will last for ten years.
At this time you will never be hungry,
because this is your wish.
What will happen next?
Your body will die,
and your soul will be there
where I came from.
What is this place?
It seems you people call him…
hell
Why is everything red?
What's going on?
I ate more than just fish!
I also ate meat!
Damn the devil!
Devil!
Hold on.
Damn the devil.
Do you know what I went through because of you?
Hold on.
- Wait!
- The scoundrel!
Through you…
- Ten years...
- Come on!
Oh, come on!
I will drag you to hell myself, devil!
Why is there no sound from him?
Need more water?
All people have their own desires
have no choice,
except to surrender to Director Jeon.
hold on
But how will he charm her without his power?
Why did he lose his strength?
Because the father moved to that woman, and...
Tell everything.
What happened to Director Jeon?
Yes, ma'am.
where is he
He said he was outside.
Probably wants to deceive me,
using health.
I want to find out everything once and…
Look at yourself.
You said you were seriously ill
but you radiate health.
Do you think I'm glowing?
However,
looks like i owe you
because you paid for the food and the rest.
This is as a token of thanks.
Didn't I say it was redundant?
I hate being in debt.
leave it I have so much money...
Still not?
...as much as you have.
Then what do you need from me?
You even lied about your health.
If it's about a deal again...
That's over.
There is no need for an agreement between us now.
Between us?
The symptoms are real.
They are so serious
that affect my existence.
What are your symptoms?
I can't do anything.
I am completely apathetic
and I feel as if I have become a different person.
I have never felt this way before.
You need to see a psychiatrist.
- Why did you come to me for...
- No.
Only you can solve my problems.
Because you are the cause of my symptoms.
Let me explain something.
I only spend time with you to
to help get well is an act of kindness.
It's not a date or anything.
give me your hand
You like to do things quickly, don't you?
Another hand.
what are you doing
We will go for a ride.
You can't believe it, that fool
dared to come here alone.
He's a loan shark, right?
What did you spend all your paychecks on?
for an Olympic medal?
Don't even ask.
Do you know any good bars? Let's go for a drink.
Alcohol, cigarettes, women...
How can you be the best athlete
if you use everything forbidden?
Geniuses don't have to work hard.
I'm just on a different level than you.
Of course.
People with innate qualities cannot be defeated.
- What the hell?
- What an idiot.
Wanted to cheer yourself up?
- Tu Hvane!
AN TU HWAN
What just…
What just happened?
They are my friends.
How many more friends do you have?
will i meet today
I want to prepare myself psychologically.
I have no friends.
So can we get down to business?
What are you talking about?
Let's try something here.
Here?
I'm not too old-fashioned myself
but this is the first time for us.
And it's not quite decent to do it in public...
What?
Where is he?
A little
come out We will do it outside.
Outside?
This is a crime.
Impropriety.
You will face up to a year behind bars
or a fine of up to five million...
Since when is walking by the river a crime?
Walk.
Get it right.
It's about timeliness.
I usually don't get ahead of things.
You can…
hold your breath a little?
Hold your breath? Why?
Well here.
He will kiss me now.
Come back. please
come back to me
So that's not the point?
Why are you so? I almost died!
- Calm down.
- How can I calm down?
How many times have I almost died today?
I nearly drowned twice because of you!
And that's not the end!
A madman is trying to kill me
and i don't even know
who is he and why does he wish me death!
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do?
Why did you do that?
I wanted to check something.
Then you should have told me in advance.
if i told you
you would refuse
Scoundrel.
I don't owe you anything.
If this is not the case, how can I get it back?
What the hell are you doing here?
I spied on To To Hee
as you told me.
It belongs to whoever found it.
So what's going on?
I thought you would charm her
instead of swimming together.
keep quiet
Is this Mrs To To Hee?
I Cha Tae Chun,
head of the financial department of Mire Group.
For now, I can only tell you,
what it can do to you
head of "Mire Group".
CEO TO TO HI
TO TO HI
Let Your Kingdom come.
May your will be done
both in heaven and on earth.
Lord, give me courage.
Give me courage to face the truth.
POMPOM PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Cute, isn't it?
Do you want one for yourself?
I will connect you now.
Be sure to post a rebuttal.
Do as I say!
I can refute the article,
which she published herself, right?
To To Hee.
I will kill you.
FEEDING THE WORLD FINANCES
GENERAL DIRECTOR: TO TO HI
FINANCIAL HEAD OF THE GROUP MR. CHA
FOUND HANGING IN THE DRESSING ROOM
Salvation comes after destruction,
when the familiar world around crumbles,
and what was normal,
ceases to be normal.
This man
broke into my difficult life.
The man is more obscure
and suspicious than all the rest.
Ku Vone, my salvation.
MY BELOVED DEMON
It is likely that you are a target.
Do you suspect someone?
I don't know who's hating
me so as to do it.
You will pay for what you have done.
You will be my bodyguard.
You tell me to protect
some insignificant person?
What will happen to my dad if I die?
Stand before me. I'll cover your back.
What is the security here?
Is it so hard to stay safe?
Then be her guardian,
if you are so worried.
My dad is safe on her wrist.
He saved me again.
Maybe the situation is not too bad.
Do you smell burning?
Spontaneous ignition
began.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel